[
    {
        "front": "<div><i><b><u>1 - How playing sports benefits your body.</u></b></i></div><div><br></div>&nbsp;The victory of the underdog over the favorite team, the last minute penalty shot that wins the tournament, the high-energy training montages.[sound:1- How playing sports.mp3]",
        "back": "A vitória do azarão sobre o time favorito, a cobrança de pênalti no último minuto que vence o campeonato, os vídeos eletrizantes com montagens/cenas dos treinos.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "&nbsp;2 -&nbsp;<u style=\"font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; \">How playing sports benefits your body.</u><div><b><i><u><br></u></i></b><div>Many people love to glorify victory on the playing field, cheer for favorite teams and play sports, but here’s a question – Should we be so obsessed with sports? Is playing sports actually as good for us as we make it out to be? Or just a fun and entertaining pastime? What does science have to say?[sound:2 - How playing sports(mp3cut.net).mp3]</div></div>",
        "back": "Muitas pessoas adoram glorificar a vitória no campo de jogo, torcer pelas equipes favoritas e praticar esportes. Mas aqui vai uma pergunta: Deveríamos ser tão obcecados por esportes? Praticar esportes é de fato tão bom para nós quando pensamos, ou é apenas um passatempo divertido e recreativo? O que a ciência tem a dizer?",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "3 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>First of all, it’s well accepted that exercise is good for our bodies and minds and that’s definitely true. Exercising, especially when we’re young, has all sorts of health benefits. Like strengthening our bones, clearing out bad cholesterol from our arteries and decreasing the risk of stroke, high blood pressure and diabetes.[sound:3 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Em primeiro lugar, é muito bem aceito que o exercício é bom para nossos corpos e &nbsp;mentes, e isso é definitivamente verdade. Exercitar-se, especialmente quando você é jovem, traz vários benefícios para a saúde, como o fortalecimento dos ossos, eliminação do colesterol ruim das nossas artérias e diminuição do risco de derrame, pressão alta e diabetes.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "4 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Our brains also release a number of chemicals when we work out – including endorphins. These natural hormones which control pain and pleasure responses in the central nervous system can lead to feelings of euphoria or what’s often called a ‘runners high’.[sound:4 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "<div>Nossos cérebros também liberam certa quantidade de substâncias quando nos exercitamos, incluindo endorfinas. Esses hormônios naturais, que controlam respostas à dor e ao prazer no sistema nervoso central, podem levar a sentimentos de euforia ou ao que é frequentemente chamado de “barato do corredor”.</div>",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "5 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Increased endorphins and consistent physical activity in general can sharpen your focus and improve your mood and memory. So does that mean we get just as much benefit going to the gym five days a week as we would joining a team and competing? Well, here’s where it gets interesting.[sound:5 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "<div>O aumento da endorfina e a constante atividade física, em geral, pode aguçar seu foco e melhorar seu humor e memória. Então, isso significa que ir à academia cinco dias por semana é tão eficiente quanto entrar em uma equipe e competir? Bem, é aqui que as coisas ficam interessantes.</div>",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "6 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Because it turns out that if you can find a sport and a team you like, studies show that there are all sorts of benefits that go beyond the physical and mental benefits of exercise alone. Some of the most significant are psychology benefits, both in the short and long term.[sound:6 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Porque acabe que se você puder encontrar um esporte e uma equipe que você goste, estudos mostram que há muitos benefícios que vão além dos benefícios físicos e mentais por si só. Alguns dos mais significantes são os benefícios psicológicos, tanto em curto como longo prazo.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "7 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Some of those come from the communal experience of being on a team. For instance, learning to trust and depend on others, to accept help, to give help and to work together towards a common goal. In addition, commitment to a team and doing something fun can also make it easier to establish a regular habit of exercise.[sound:7 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Alguns deles vêm da experiência compartilhada de se estar em uma equipe. Por exemplo, aprender a confiar e a depender dos outros, aceitar ajuda, oferecer ajuda e trabalhar em conjunto visando um objetivo comum. Além disso, ter compromisso com uma equipe, fazendo algo divertido, pode também tornar fácil estabelecer um hábito regular de exercício.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "8 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>School sport participation has also been shown to reduce the risk of suffering from depression for up to four years. Meanwhile, your self-esteem and confidence can get a big boost. There are a few reasons for that.[sound:8 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "A participação em jogos escolares também tem mostrado ser eficiente na redução do risco de sofrer depressão por até quatro anos. Além do mais, sua autoestima e confiança podem dar um grande salto. Há alguns motivos para isso.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "9 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>One is found in training. Just by working and working at skills, especially with a good coach, you reinforce a growth mindset within yourself. That’s when you say ‘Even if I can’t do something today, I can improve myself through practice and achieve it eventually’. That mindset is useful in all walks of life.[sound:9 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Um está em treinar. Só pelo fato de desenvolver suas habilidades, especialmente com um bom treinador, você reforça uma mentalidade de crescimento dentro de si mesmo. É quando você diz: “Mesmo que eu não consiga fazer algo hoje, eu posso ficar melhor através da prática e, finalmente, atingir meu objetivo”. Essa mentalidade é útil para todos os estilos de vida.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "10 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br></u></i></b></div><div>And then there’s learning through failure, one of the most transformative, long-term benefits of playing sports. The experience of coming to terms with defeat can build the resilience and self-awareness necessary to manage academic, social and physical hurdles. So even if your team isn’t winning all the time, or at all, there is a real benefit to your experience.[sound:10 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "E então há o aprendizado através do fracasso, um dos benefícios mais transformadores e duradouros na prática de esportes. A experiência de conviver com a derrota pode construir a resiliência e a autoconsciência necessárias para lidar com obstáculos acadêmicos, sociais e físicos. Então, mesmo que sua equipe não esteja ganhando o tempo todo, ou esteja perdendo, existe um benefício real através da experiência.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "11 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Now, not everyone will enjoy every sport. Perhaps one team is too competitive or not competitive enough. It can also take time to find a sport that will play to your strengths – That’s completely okay. But if you spend some time looking, you’ll be able to find a sport that fits your individual needs.[sound:11 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "No entanto, nem todo mundo vai gostar de todos os esportes. Talvez uma equipe seja muito competitiva ou não competitiva o suficiente. Também pode levar tempo para encontrar um esporte que irá se aplicar aos seus pontos fortes. É perfeitamente normal. Mas se você passar um tempo procurando, será capaz de encontrar um esporte que atenda suas necessidades individuais.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "12 - <b><i><u>How playing sports benefits your body.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>And if you do, there are so many benefits. You’ll be a part of a supportive community. You’ll be building your confidence. You’ll be exercising your body and nurturing your mind. Not to mention, having fun.[sound:12 - How playing sports (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "E, se você encontrar, há muitos benefícios. Você será parte de uma comunidade solidária. Você estará melhorando sua confiança. Você estará exercitando seu corpo e alimentado sua mente, sem mencionar o divertimento.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1 - <b><i><u>How to stay motivated when learning a language.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>In my experience, the difference between people who are successful at learning languages and people who are not is this: People who often give up approach learning languages with a couple of specific questions. &nbsp;They often want to know: How long exactly is this going to take me to do and how much of my time am I going to have to give every day in order to be able to do this.[sound:1 - How to stay motivated when learning a language (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Pela (em) minha experiência, a diferença entre as pessoas bem-sucedidas em aprender idiomas e pessoas que não são é esta: as pessoas que normalmente desistem, abordam o aprendizado de idiomas com algumas perguntas específicas. Elas normalmente querem saber: quanto tempo exatamente vai levar para eu fazer isso e quanto do meu tempo eu terei que dedicar todo dia para ser capaz de fazer isso.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "2 - <b><i><u>How to stay motivated when learning a language.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>The reason why is because they don’t really like learning languages. They like speaking languages and they like the idea of the benefits of it, but they’re not necessarily enjoying the process of learning them. In order to make your language-learning a lot more fun, I think you should focus on the things that interest you the most.[sound:2 - How to stay motivated when learning a language (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "A razão disso é porque elas não gostam realmente de aprender idiomas. Elas gostam de falar idiomas e gostam da ideia dos benefícios disso, mas não estão necessariamente aproveitando o processo de aprendê-las. Para tornar o seu aprendizado de idiomas muito mais divertido, eu acho que você deve focar em coisas que mais te interessam.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "3 - <b><i><u>How to stay motivated when learning a language.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>If you want to learn the language to learn more about the culture, then you should be watching films, you should be reading and enjoying those things that are available. It’s also important to reward yourself for the learning that you’re doing, so make sure that you give yourself a little treat and maybe even plan a holiday or a trip to the country where they speak the language, so you can actually see how much progress you’ve made since you started learning and how far you could still come in a similar amount of time.[sound:3 - How to stay motivated when learning a language (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Se você quiser aprender o idioma para aprender mais sobre a cultura, então você deveria assistir filmes, você deveria estar lendo e aproveitando essas coisas que estão disponíveis. Também é importante se recompensar pelo aprendizado que você está tendo, então certifique-se de se dar um pequeno prêmio/recompensa e talvez até mesmo planejar férias ou uma viagem para o país onde falam a língua, então você pode ver de fato quanto progresso fez desde que começou a aprender e quão longe você ainda poderia ir em um espaço de tempo semelhante.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "4 - <b><i><u>How stay motivated when learning a language.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>The other really important thing is to set realistic goals when thinking about learning a language. That well may keep you much more motivated through the language-learning process and make sure that you stick to the commitment that you make. So, an example of an unrealistic goal is: ‘I want to be able to speak German fluently.’ That’s very, very difficult to achieve and it’s gonna take you a long time.[sound:4 - How to stay motivated when learning a language (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "A (uma) outra coisa realmente importante é estabelecer objetivos realistas ao pensar em aprender um idioma. Isso pode muito bem mantê-lo muito mais motivado durante o processo de aprendizado do idioma e garantir que você se mantenha no compromisso que você fizer. Então, um exemplo de um objetivo irrealista é: “Eu quero ser capaz de falar alemão fluentemente. “ Isso é muito, muito difícil de se alcançar e vai levar muito tempo.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "5 - <b><i><u>&nbsp;How to stay motivated when learning a language.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>But an example of a realistic goal would be something like: ‘I would like to have a ten-minute conversation with a native speaker about something very simple and easy.’ Or, for example: ‘I want to be able to watch the news and understand fifty per cent of it.’ That’s something that is very clear and that you could work towards in order to make sure that you keep seeing how much progress you make.[sound:5 - How to stay motivated when learning a language(mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Mas um exemplo de objetivo realista seria algo como: “Eu gostaria de ter uma conversa de dez minutos com um falante nativo sobre algo muito simples e fácil”. Ou, por exemplo: “Eu quero ser capaz de assistir às notícias e entender cinquenta por cento (disso). Isso é algo que é muito claro e em que você poderia trabalhar para garantir que continua vendo quanto progresso você faz.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "6 - <u style=\"font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; \">&nbsp;How to stay motivated when learning a language.</u><div><u style=\"font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; \"><br /></u></div><div>Share your language-learning tips and experiences by leaving a comment below, and make sure you check out the other videos in this series.[sound:6 - How to stay motivated when learning a language(mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Compartilhe suas dicas de aprendizado de idiomas e experiências deixando um comentário abaixo, e certifique-se de dar uma olhada nos outros vídeos desta série.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "<div>1 -&nbsp;<u style=\"font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; \">Your brain on coffee.</u></div><div><br /></div>With its stimulating effects, it’s easy to understand why coffee is the second most traded commodity on earth after oil. For many, it keeps us awake and moving through our busy days. But how does it work? What exactly does coffee do to your brain?[sound:1 - Coffee(mp3cut.net).mp3]",
        "back": "Com seus efeitos estimuladores, é fácil compreender porque o café é a segunda commodity mais vendida na terra, depois do óleo. Para muitos, ele mantém-nos acordados e movendo-se pelos nossos dias ocupados. Mas como isso funciona? O que exatamente o café faz ao seu cérebro?",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "<div>2 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b></div><div><br /></div>Whenever you’re awake, a chemical called adenosine slowly accumulates in your brain and this adenosine binds to receptors which slow down brain activity. Ultimately, the more adenosine there is, the more tired your brain feels. Which makes sense as the longer you’re awake, the more fatigued you become. Conversely, while you sleep, the concentration of adenosine declines, gradually promoting wakefulness.[sound:2 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]",
        "back": "Sempre que você está acordado, uma química chamada adenosina acumula-se lentamente no seu cérebro e essa adenosina liga-se a receptores que retardam a atividade cerebral. Em última análise, quanto mais adenosina houver, mais cansado seu cérebro se sente. O que faz sentido já que, por quanto mais tempo você fica acordado, mais fatigado você se torna. Por outro lado, enquanto você dorme, a concentração da adenosina declina, gradualmente promovendo vigília.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "<div>3 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b></div><div><br /></div>But it turns out that the caffeine in your coffee is incredibly similar to adenosine in structure. The caffeine works its way through your bloodstream and into your brain where it starts to compete and combines with adenosine receptors. But because it’s not adenosine, the sleepiness effect isn’t felt. Adenosine can no longer bind, meaning its calming properties are diminished. Which is great for you when you’re feeling tired.[sound:3 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]",
        "back": "Mas acontece que a cafeína no seu café é incrivelmente semelhante à adenosina, em estrutura. A cafeína consegue chegar até sua corrente sanguínea e até o seu cérebro, onde ela começa a competir e combinar-se com receptores de adenosina. Mas porque não é adenosina, o efeito de sonolência não é sentido. A adenosina já não consegue mais ligar, ou seja, suas propriedades calmantes são diminuídas. O que é ótimo para você, quando você está se sentindo cansado.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "4 - <u style=\"font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; \">Your brain on coffee.</u>&nbsp;<div><br /></div><div>However, with long term use of caffeine, your brain responds by creating more adenosine receptors, which means more caffeine is required to elicit the same response. It also means that when you try to quit drinking coffee or miss your daily intake, you might experience some withdrawal symptoms and feel more tired than you would have before you ever drank coffee. But the caffeine doesn’t stop there.[sound:4 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "No entanto, com a utilização prolongada de cafeína, seu cérebro responde criando mais receptores de adenosina, o que significa que mais cafeína é necessária para elicitar a mesma resposta. Significa também que, quando você tenta parar de beber café ou perde sua ingestão diária, você pode experienciar alguns sintomas de abstinência e se sentir mais cansado do que você iria se sentir antes que você bebesse café. Mas a cafeína não para por aí.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "5 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>It also stimulates the production of adrenaline – you know, the fight or flight hormone. This increases your heart rate, gets your blood pumping and even opens up your airways. Furthermore, it affects dopamine levels by preventing its reabsorption in the brain, which makes you feel happy. In fact, this is the exact same thing that cocaine does, just to a lesser degree. It’s a drug after all.[sound:5 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Ela também estimula a produção de adrenalina – você sabe, o hormônio do “lute ou fuja”. Isso aumenta sua frequência cardíaca, coloca seu sangue para bombear e até abre suas vias aéreas. Além disso, ela afeta os níveis de dopamina, impedindo sua reabsorção no cérebro, o que faz você se sentir feliz. Na verdade, esta é a exata mesma coisa que a cocaína faz, apenas em menor grau. É uma droga, afinal de contas.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "6 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>This dopamine stimulation is also the aspect of coffee that makes it moderately addictive. So, can you drink too much coffee? It turns out there is a lethal dose of caffeine, which is somewhere around 150 milligrams of caffeine per kilogram of your body. This means if you weigh 70 kilograms, you require 14,000 milligrams of caffeine to overdose.[sound:6 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Esta estimulação de dopamina é também o aspecto do café que o torna moderadamente viciante. Então, é possível beber café em demasia?¹ Descobriu-se que há uma dose letal de cafeína, que está em algum lugar ao redor de 150 mg de cafeína por quilograma de seu corpo. Isso significa que se você pesa 70 kg, você exige 14.000 miligramas de cafeína para ter overdose.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "7 - <b><i><u>&nbsp;Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Put into perspective, an average cup of coffee contains roughly 150 milligrams of caffeine. Meaning if you’re 70 kilograms, approximately 70 cups of coffee would kill you. However, you would have to drink those cups all at once, making it effectively impossible to overdose on caffeine from coffee, since you wouldn’t be able to physically fit that much in your stomach.[sound:7 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Posta em perspectiva, uma xícara média de café contém aproximadamente 150 mg de cafeína. Ou seja, se você pesa 70 quilogramas, aproximadamente 70 xícaras de café iriam matar você. No entanto, você teria de beber essas xícaras todas de uma vez, tornando efetivamente impossível a overdose de cafeína através do café, dado que você não seria capaz de armazenar fisicamente essa quantidade em seu estômago.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "8 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div><div>You would also start experiencing mania and hallucinations before getting to this point. Caffeine also has a half-life of around 6 hours. So, if you drank a standard coffee with around 150 milligrams of caffeine, after about six hours, there would only be around 75 milligrams left in your system and you’ll be feeling half of the effect.[sound:8 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div></div>",
        "back": "Você iria também começar a experienciar euforia e alucinações antes de chegar a este ponto. Cafeína também tem uma meia-vida de cerca de 6 horas. Então, se você bebesse um café padrão com cerca de 150 miligramas de cafeína, após cerca de seis horas, haveria apenas cerca de 75 miligramas restantes em seu sistema e você estaria sentindo metade do efeito.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "9 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>And 6 hours after that, you’ll have 37.5 milligrams, leaving more room for adenosine to jump back into action, which is why you may reach for another cup throughout the day to remain that glorious alert and energetic feeling. So, drink up and enjoy the buzz while it lasts.[sound:9 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "E 6 horas depois disso, você teria 37,5 miligramas, deixando mais espaço para adenosina saltar de volta à ação, razão pela qual você talvez recorra a outra xícara ao longo do dia para manter aquele glorioso sentimento alerta e enérgico. Então, beba e desfrute da excitação enquanto ela dura.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "10 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>And for all of you who are in school, while we know that caffeine is key, so are good deals on textbooks. So, we’ve teamed up with slugbooks.com to get you the cheapest prices for the books you need. All you have to do is head to 10 – slugbooks.com/asapSCIENCE and search the ISBN number of the books you’re looking for. SlugBooks will then compare prices from all across the net.[sound:10 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "E para todos vocês que estão na escola, enquanto sabemos que a cafeína é a chave, igualmente são bons negócios em livros didáticos. Então, nós fizemos uma parceria com slugbooks.com para conseguí-los os preços mais baratos para os livros que você necessita. Tudo o que você precisa fazer é ir para slugbooks.com/asapSCIENCE e pesquisar o número ISBN dos livros que você está procurando. SlugBooks irá então comparar preços de toda a internet.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "11 - <b><i><u>Your brain on coffee.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Seriously, we know how expensive textbooks can be so hopefully this will save you some money. Got a burning question you want answered? Ask it in the comments or on Facebook and twitter, and subscribe for more weekly science videos.[sound:11 - Your Brain On Coffee (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Sério, sabemos como os livros didáticos podem ser caros, então esperançosamente isso vai lhe poupar algum dinheiro. Tem uma pergunta ardente que você quer respondida? Pergunte-a nos comentários ou no Facebook e no twitter, e inscreva-se para mais vídeos semanais de ciência.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1 - <i><u><b>How to study smarter, not harder.</b></u></i><div><br /></div><div>Consistency has been a hallmark of good study habits since the 1900s. It’s drilled into our heads from an early age – have a dedicated desk, have a dedicated time, eliminate distractions. But what if almost everything we’re told about how we learn is wrong? What if being inconsistent can work in our favor?[sound:1 - How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 (mp3cut.net).mp3]</div>",
        "back": "A consistência tem sido uma marca registrada dos bons hábitos de estudo desde os anos 1900. Isso entrou na nossa cabeça quando ainda éramos pequenos – tenha uma mesa dedicada a isso, dedique um tempo específico, elimine as distrações. Mas e se quase tudo que nos contaram sobre como aprendemos estiver errado? E se ser inconsistente puder funcionar ao nosso favor?",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "2 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>For instance, could something as simple as a change in venue make a difference? Could interrupting work on a large project facilitate more inventive thinking? In the mid 1970s a trio of psychologists performed an experiment to answer just that. They wondered what would happen if people studied the same material twice, only in two different places.[sound:2-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593140689.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Por exemplo, poderia algo tão simples quanto a mudança de local fazer diferença? Poderia a interrupção no trabalho de um grande projeto facilitar o pensamento mais criativo? No meio dos anos 70 um trio de psicólogos realizou um experimento para responder exatamente isso. Eles queriam saber o que aconteceria se as pessoas estudassem o mesmo conteúdo duas vezes, só que em dois lugares diferentes.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "3 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>To test this, they presented a group of students with a list of 40 four-lettered words like ‘ball’ and ‘fork’. All of the students were given two ten-minute study sessions, but half of them studied in the same dimly lighted cluttered room for both sessions, while the other half studied in two different rooms – the cluttered one and a neater, brighter one across campus.[sound:3-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593353708.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Para testar isso, eles apresentaram a um grupo de alunos uma lista com 40 palavras de 4 letras cada, como “Ball” e “Fork”. Foi dado a todos os alunos duas seções de estudos de dez minutos, mas metade deles estudaram as duas seções na mesma sala bagunçada e mal iluminada, enquanto a outra metade estudou em duas salas diferentes – a sala bagunçada e uma mais arrumada e com mais luz do outro lado do campus.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "4 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>In the last phase of the experiment, researchers had the students write down as many of the study words as they could in ten minutes. The difference in scores were striking. The one room group recalled an average of 16 of the 40 study words. The two-rooms group recalled 24. A simple change in venue had improved the student’s memory by 40%.[sound:4-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593517693.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Na última fase do experimento, os pesquisadores pediram aos alunos que anotassem o máximo possível das palavras que eles tinham estudado em dez minutos. A diferença de pontuação foi impressionante. O grupo que estudou em uma sala lembrou uma média de 16 das 40 palavras. O grupo das duas salas lembrou 24. Uma simples mudança de local tinha melhorado a memória dos alunos em 40%.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "5 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>But it isn’t just where you study or practice, how you do so is also part of the environment. Think about it – writing notes by hand is one kind of activity, typing them is another. The same goes for studying while standing up, versus sitting down, versus running on a treadmill. In the end, it doesn’t matter which aspects of the environment you vary, so long as you vary what you can.[sound:5-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593654006.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Mas não é só onde você estuda ou pratica, como você faz isso também é parte do ambiente. Pense nisso – escrever notas a mão é um tipo de atividade, digitá-las é outra. O mesmo acontece com estudar de pé em vez de sentado, ou correndo em uma esteira. No fim das contas, não importa quais aspectos do ambiente você varia, contanto que você varie o que conseguir.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "6 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Despite what traditional advice tells us, when it comes to learning, it’s consistency, not change, that is limited. So, next time you need to study, to practice or prepare for that big project, mix it up. Try another room, another time of day. Take your guitar to the park, change coffee shops, switch practice courts, read in silence and with music on.[sound:6-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593792164.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Apesar do que o conselho tradicional nos diz, quando se trata de aprender é a consistência e não a mudança que é limitada. Então, na próxima vez que você precisar estudar, praticar ou se preparar para aquele grande projeto, misture tudo. Experimente outra sala, outra hora do dia. Leve seu violão para o parque, mude de cafés (lojas de café), mude de quadra de esportes, leia em silêncio e com música.",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "7 - <b><i><u>How to study smarter, not harder.</u></i></b><div><b><i><u><br /></u></i></b></div><div>Why? Because each alteration of your routine further enriches the skills being rehearsed, making them more accessible to you for a longer period of time. That’s the soul of real learning after all – to carry the skills and the knowledge with you, available when needed, no matter the environment. How We Learn, by Benedict Carey on sale September 9th.[sound:7-How to study smarter_ not harder - From How We Lea - 128K MP3 AETrim1493593887083.mp3]</div>",
        "back": "Por que? Porque cada alteração da sua rotina enriquece mais as habilidades que estão sendo ensaiadas, tornando-as mais acessíveis a você por um período de tempo maior. Essa é a alma do aprendizado real no fim das contas – manter as habilidades e o conhecimento com você, disponível quando preciso, não importa o ambiente. Como Aprendemos, de Benedict Carey, à venda em 9 de setembro.",
        "order": 0
    }
]